{
    "subject": "resource/AJ_Michalka",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:21st-century_American_singers",
    "human_readable": "AJ Michalka is a subject of the category 21st-century American singers.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8252525329589844,
            "question": "What century is AJ Michalka part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7933897972106934,
            "question": "What type of performer is AJ Michalka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7784898281097412,
            "question": "Is AJ Michalka considered a contemporary musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7497388124465942,
            "question": "Is AJ Michalka known for singing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6070234775543213,
            "question": "Where is AJ Michalka from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5091226696968079,
            "question": "What musical genre(s) is AJ Michalka associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4379085600376129,
            "question": "What decade was AJ Michalka born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43235763907432556,
            "question": "Has AJ Michalka achieved fame in the music industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4218742251396179,
            "question": "In what country was AJ Michalka born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41177430748939514,
            "question": "What is AJ Michalka's primary profession?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=AJ Michalka is a subject of the category 21st-century American singers.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6766_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country was AJ Michalka born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6766_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has AJ Michalka achieved fame in the music industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6766_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What decade was AJ Michalka born in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6766_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6766_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6766_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6766_142.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6766_166.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6766_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6766_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6766_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6766_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6766_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6766_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's my evaluation:\n\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain information that AJ Michalka is an actress, singer, and songwriter, and she is part of the musical duo Aly & AJ. This suggests that she is a subject of the category 21st-century American singers."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents state that AJ Michalka is an \"American actress, singer, and songwriter\" and mentions her involvement in music, including being part of the musical duo Aly & AJ and performing at various music festivals. This supports the categorization of AJ Michalka as a 21st-century American singer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}